

# JUAN DE SANTOS

#### JR. FRONT-END DEVELOPER

+49 0178 6082868

juanj.desantos@gmail.com

Portfolio: J.DEV

Berlin, Germany.

HELLO, I'm Jr. Front-End Developer from Spain, currently residing in Germany since 2018, with a background in others work fields. In 2022, I made the decision to embrace new challenges and explore the programming world. The learning process, which initially presented difficulties, unexpectedly revealed a source of joy and satisfaction. I've gained previous experience in developing my own projects and am looking for the opportunity to work as a professional programmer.

### **SKILLS**

Hard-working

Look for solutions

Dedicated

Enthusiastic

Methodical

Trustworthy

Team Player

## **KNOWLEDGE**



HTML



CSS



Javascript



React



API



Github



Scrum

## LANGUAGES

English B1 • • • 0 0 0

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### > RETTUNGSSANITÄTER

Gorris Krankentransport GmbH. Berlin, Germany. *Apr 2018 - Jun 2023* 

Responsible for transporting patients from point A to point B while also providing emotional support and empathy. In addition, management of Human Resources tasks, including recruiting new colleagues in Spain, as well

#### > TECHNICIAN AND EVENT ASSISTANT

as managing and translating during job interviews.

Track 13 S.L. Segovia, Spain.

Jun 2016 - Mar 2018

Management of motor vehicles and transport of materials to events providing audiovisual services across Spain. During these events, I also provided technical assistance.

## > DATA PROTECTION CONSULTANT

Segoval S.L. Segovia, Spain.

Feb 2016 - Jun 2016

Assisting companies with implementing Constitutional Law related to data protection. My responsibilities included acquiring new clients and providing technical advice on-site.

# > PRODUCTION TECHNICIAN FOR EVENTS AND SHOWS

Dos Eventos S.L. Segovia, Spain.

Oct 2008 - Nov 2015

Transportation, organization and assembly management for events of any size.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### > FRONT END DEVELOPER

Developer Akademie. Münich, Germany. 2023

#### > SPECIALIST IN EMERGENCY HEALT CARE

I.E.S. Ezequiel González. Segovia, Spain.

2017